<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>!!Con West on !!Con West : Joy, Surprise, and Excitement of Computing!</title>
    <link>http://bangbangcon.com/west/</link>
    <description>Recent content in !!Con West on !!Con West : Joy, Surprise, and Excitement of Computing!</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Feb 2019 20:23:00 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://bangbangcon.com/west/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Program</title>
      <link>http://bangbangcon.com/west/program/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Feb 2019 20:23:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bangbangcon.com/west/program/</guid>
      <description>Conference program Jump directly to the Saturday or Sunday program!

Saturday, 23 February 2019     Time Event     9:00am Space opens (please don&amp;rsquo;t arrive before nine!)   9:00 - 10:30am Registration; continental breakfast; mingling   10:30 - 11:10am Opening remarks and keynote talk: The Best Parts! Of My Favorite Things!&amp;nbsp; (Lynn Cyrin)   11:10 - 11:25am Break!   11:25am - 12:15pm First Session!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sponsor !!Con West!</title>
      <link>http://bangbangcon.com/west/sponsors/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2018 13:46:46 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bangbangcon.com/west/sponsors/</guid>
      <description>Sponsor !!Con West! !!Con is a tremendous amount of fun, and we think that it brings a lot of value to its attendees, and to the programming community at large. But !!Con also costs money to run, and we&amp;rsquo;re committed to making sure that it remains affordable to everybody who wants to participate.
As such, we need your help to keep !!Con West open and available to all. In exchange, we&amp;rsquo;d love to help put your company in front of our 200+ smart, creative, thoughtful participants.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Speakers</title>
      <link>http://bangbangcon.com/west/speakers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2018 13:40:03 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bangbangcon.com/west/speakers/</guid>
      <description>Who&amp;rsquo;s speaking at !!Con West? Keynote Speakers Lynn Cyrin The Best Parts! Of My Favorite Things!
The software engineering ecosystem is so big! How can you tell which tool is best for which job, and what&amp;rsquo;s going to give you the simplest path to get a job done? How do all of the various systems and tools complement each other? These are all questions you will have to answer on a regular basis, and I want to help you!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Conduct</title>
      <link>http://bangbangcon.com/west/conduct/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2018 13:39:05 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bangbangcon.com/west/conduct/</guid>
      <description>Code of conduct Our goal with !!Con West is to bring the US west coast computing community together for a conference about the excitement, joy, and surprise of computing.
We value the participation of each member of the community and want all attendees to have an enjoyable and fulfilling experience. Accordingly, all attendees are expected to show respect and courtesy to other attendees throughout the conference and at all conference events, whether officially sponsored by !</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Here</title>
      <link>http://bangbangcon.com/west/venue/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2018 13:38:57 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bangbangcon.com/west/venue/</guid>
      <description>Getting to !!Con West 2019 We&amp;rsquo;re excited to bring !!Con West 2019 to scenic Santa Cruz, California, on the campus of UC Santa Cruz, on February 23rd and 24th. Santa Cruz is a joy of coastal California redwoods, about an hour&amp;rsquo;s drive from the bustle of Silicon Valley. We&amp;rsquo;ll be holding !!Con West in the Jack Baskin Auditorium from about 10am to 5pm each day.
.mapouter{text-align:right;height:500px;width:600px;}.gmap_canvas {overflow:hidden;background:none!important;height:500px;width:600px;} Getting to Santa Cruz By car  The best way to get to Santa Cruz from most of the Peninsula is by way of CA-17, which takes you from CA-85 through the Santa Cruz mountains into the city; Please ensure to leave sufficiently early as CA-17 gets heavy traffic southbound on weekends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Call for Proposals!</title>
      <link>http://bangbangcon.com/west/cfp/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2018 13:06:41 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bangbangcon.com/west/cfp/</guid>
      <description>Give a talk at !!Con West! Our call for talk proposals is now closed. Thanks to everyone who submitted a proposal!
Hi! !!Con West is excited to be launching our inaugural west coast conference celebrating the joy, excitement, and surprise of computing, and we want you to submit a talk proposal. The submission deadline is Friday, November 30.
Since its launch five years ago, !!Con talks have featured everything from glowing mushrooms to game theory; from machine knitting to geolocation; from live coding on an Apple II to queer feminist cyberpunk manifestos.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FAQs</title>
      <link>http://bangbangcon.com/west/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bangbangcon.com/west/faq/</guid>
      <description>Frequently asked questions What&amp;rsquo;s all this, then? !!Con (pronounced &amp;ldquo;bang bang con&amp;rdquo;) is a two-day conference of ten-minute talks about the joy, excitement, and surprise of computing that&amp;rsquo;s been held annually in New York since 2014. Due to massive demand, in 2019 we&amp;rsquo;re expanding !!Con to the west coast of the US! !!Con West will be held in Santa Cruz, California, on the campus of UC Santa Cruz, on February 23-24, 2019.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>