<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>!!Con West on !!Con West : Joy, Surprise, and Excitement of Computing!</title>
    <link>http://bangbangcon.com/west/</link>
    <description>Recent content in !!Con West on !!Con West : Joy, Surprise, and Excitement of Computing!</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2019 10:52:57 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://bangbangcon.com/west/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Here</title>
      <link>http://bangbangcon.com/west/venue/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2019 10:52:57 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bangbangcon.com/west/venue/</guid>
      <description>Getting to !!Con West 2020 We&amp;rsquo;re excited to bring !!Con West 2020 to scenic Santa Cruz, California, on the campus of UC Santa Cruz, from February 29 to March 1. Santa Cruz is a joy of coastal California redwoods, about an hour&amp;rsquo;s drive from the bustle of Silicon Valley. We will hold !!Con West in the Jack Baskin Auditorium, with registration starting at 9am each day, and talks ending around 5pm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Call for Proposals!</title>
      <link>http://bangbangcon.com/west/cfp/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2019 10:48:41 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bangbangcon.com/west/cfp/</guid>
      <description>The !!Con West 2020 Call for Proposals is closed Thank you to everyone who submitted a proposal for !!Con West 2020! The Call for Proposals is now closed. If you missed submitting to !!Con West 2020, please consider submitting to !!Con 2020 instead!
Give a talk at !!Con West! Hi! !!Con West is back for our second year of celebrating the joy, excitement, and surprise of computing, and we want you to submit a talk proposal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Conduct</title>
      <link>http://bangbangcon.com/west/conduct/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2019 10:57:05 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bangbangcon.com/west/conduct/</guid>
      <description>Code of conduct We value the participation of each member of the !!Con West community and want all attendees to have an enjoyable and fulfilling experience. Accordingly, all attendees are expected to show respect and courtesy to other attendees throughout the conference and at all conference events, whether officially sponsored by !!Con West or not.
All attendees, speakers, exhibitors, organizers and volunteers at any !!Con West event are required to observe the following Code of Conduct.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sponsor !!Con West!</title>
      <link>http://bangbangcon.com/west/sponsors/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2018 13:46:46 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bangbangcon.com/west/sponsors/</guid>
      <description>Sponsor !!Con West! !!Con is a tremendous amount of fun, and we think that it brings a lot of value to its attendees, and to the programming community at large. But !!Con also costs money to run, and we&amp;rsquo;re committed to making sure that it remains affordable to everybody who wants to participate.
As such, we need your help to keep !!Con West open and available to all. In exchange, we&amp;rsquo;d love to help put your company in front of our 200+ smart, creative, thoughtful participants.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Speakers</title>
      <link>http://bangbangcon.com/west/speakers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2018 13:40:03 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bangbangcon.com/west/speakers/</guid>
      <description>Who&amp;rsquo;s speaking at !!Con West? Keynote Speakers isis agora lovecruft isis lovecruft is a cryptographer who has contributed to Signal, The Tor Project, the Electronic Frontier Foundation, and many others. They enjoy making fast, safe, and hard-to-misuse cryptographic libraries in Rust, walking through woods with their wolfhound familiar, and casting curses on evildoers in tech to turn them into umbrellas.
Erin Rose Glass Erin Glass is a writer, consultant, and librarian at UC San Diego, where she advises on emerging forms of digital research, education, infrastructure, and community.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FAQs</title>
      <link>http://bangbangcon.com/west/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bangbangcon.com/west/faq/</guid>
      <description>Frequently asked questions What&amp;rsquo;s all this? !!Con (pronounced &amp;ldquo;bang bang con&amp;rdquo;) is a two-day conference of ten-minute talks about the joy, excitement, and surprise of computing that&amp;rsquo;s been held annually in New York since 2014. Due to massive demand, !!Con was expanded to the west coast of the US in 2019. We are so excited to bring !!Con West back in 2020, and it will be held in Santa Cruz, California, on the campus of UC Santa Cruz, on February 29th and March 1st.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>